[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the second-tallest waterfall on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Tugela Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Temola Falls", "Tierra Falls", "Tamilla Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Rocky win the exhibition match in the film Rocky Balboa?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sheep are similar to cows in that they have a stomach which contains four chambers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what day of the week does the parade of the famous Rio Carnival traditionally start?", "correct_answer": "Sunday", "incorrect_answers": ["Thursday", "Wednesday", "Friday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which battleship of the Imperial Japanese Navy was sent on a suicide mission in 1945, during the invasion of Okinawa?", "correct_answer": "Yamato", "incorrect_answers": ["Kamikaze", "Tojo", "Noh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the few non-fish oils that contains linolenic acid, an omega-3 fatty acid. This will lower your chances of having a heart disease. It also contains no cholesterol.", "correct_answer": "Soybean oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunflower oil", "Olive oil", "Palm oil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Rosie make a boat for Carter and her father in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Researches have found that most graffiti artists fall into this demographic category.", "correct_answer": "Males of age 12 to 21", "incorrect_answers": ["Females of age 25 to 35", "Females of age 12 to 21", "Males of age 25 to 35"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While playing gin rummy in the final scene of this movie, C.C. Baxter confesses his love for Fran, who simply tells him to \u201cShut up and deal.\u201d", "correct_answer": "The Apartment", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hustler", "Some like it Hot", "Tom Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the man who invented logarithms?", "correct_answer": "John Napier", "incorrect_answers": ["Rene Descartes", "Blaise Pascal", "Robert Recorde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals only has molars?", "correct_answer": "Adult aardvarks", "incorrect_answers": ["Adult penguins", "Adult  wolves", "Adult minnows"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the listed African countries does not border a sea or an ocean?", "correct_answer": "Malawi", "incorrect_answers": ["Madagascar", "Mozambique", "Mauritania"]}]